exposureroom.com 2011-10-05

# ExposureRoom.com Privacy Policy

### ExposureRoom.com Privacy Policy

At ExposureRoom we recognize that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use ExposureRoom's services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. 

By using or accessing ExposureRoom.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Information Collected

  * ExposureRoom collects personal information when you register for ExposureRoom or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. 
  * You Email address, postal address, date of birth and other personal information you provide will not be made public. However, your ExposureRoom username and your first and last name are in the public domain and will likely be indexed by global search engines and the ExposureRoom search engine. 
  * ExposureRoom uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use ExposureRoom services in order to improve the quality of our services. 
  * You post User Content on the Site at your own risk. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.
  * If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. 
  * ExposureRoom stores this information to send this one-time invitation, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at support@exposureroom.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

#### Use of Information

  * We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. 
  * We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve ExposureRoom services. 
  * When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services. 
  * ExposureRoom may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, a member response to your newsgroup post, or someone comments on your asset, you may receive an email alerting you to that fact.
  * ExposureRoom processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America.

#### Your choices

  * You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result. 
  * We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible. 

ExposureRoom.com may modify this Policy from time to time and such modification shall be effective upon posting by ExposureRoom.com on the ExposureRoom Website. You agree to be bound to any changes to this Policy when you use the ExposureRoom Services after any such modification is posted. It is therefore important that you review this Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes.

If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact [privacy@ExposureRoom.com](mailto:privacy@exposureroom.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy), Subject: Privacy Policy.
